MARILIAGILP

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT

- 343 777 8289
- mariliagilp@gmail.com
- Ottawa, ON
- http://gilp0025.github.io

SKILLS

- User-centered design
- UX/Ui
- Usability best practices
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Develop wireframes
- HTML, CSS and Bootstrap
- WordPress and Shopify
- InVision and Adobe XD
- Creating clickable prototypes
- Microsoft Office

EDUCATION

Interactive Media Design | Diploma

Algonquin College 2019 – Current

Art Direction and Creative Advertisement | Open Course

Miami Ad School 2016 – 2018

Digital Communications and Multimedia Design | Bachelor

Anhanguera Educacional 2004 – 2007

PROFILE

Interactive Multimedia Designer with 2+ years of experience in the field of graphic design – having worked on an extensive range of projects in the areas of web design and advertisement. Organized, positive, creative, problem-solver, with a keen eye for detail, a strong technical ability adapted to fast-paced environments working as a team member or independently, and a boundless enthusiasm for everything related to design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CANOA DIGITAL | 2019 - PRESENT

- Work with a team of four to develop on a daily basis social media ads, online campaigns, and deliver design solutions for more than 3 clients
- Create a visual identity manual and ensured the brand's consistency across projects and different platforms
- Design, develop and deploy 8 WordPress website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap 3 framework with user experience in mind

PRODUCT DESIGNER

NERDSTORE | LOCATION | 2018

- Reviewed and analyzed industry trends to support the development of new products in collaboration with account, creative and studio teams
- Developed visual concepts for home products, collectibles, and clothing within the nerd and geek theme
- Created moodboard to set the tone of voice for illustrations, packaging and labels used by freelancers for more than 20 different products.

ART DIRECTOR

ISOBAR | 2017

- Provided visual identity to small and medium companies strengthening their online presence
- Helped to create unique cross-platform solutions using design thinking concepts to handle communications between customer and business companies
- Prepared layouts for email marketing, banners, social media posts, and promotional advertising for 4 accounts

MARILIAGILP

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

AWARDS

Dean's Honours List of Outstanding Academic Achievement

Algonquin College Term 2, Year 1 - 2021

Dean's Honours List of Outstanding Academic Achievement

Algonquin College Term 1, Year 1 - 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

ART DIRECTOR

AGÊNCIA TUDO | 2015 - 2017

- Developed graphic and digital materials for 20 corporate events, fairs, conventions
- Created logos, graphic and digital materials and concepts for stands and kiosks, monitoring their effectiveness and people engagement in 20 events.
- Collaborated with external design team and internal staff to create and launch events with 250k people attending daily

OTHER EXPERIENCES

STUDENT LEADERSHIP PROGRAM

ALGONQUIN COLLEGE | 2021

• Took part in a series of experiential workshops and leadership opportunities to explore and enhance leadership skills and help to gain the knowledge of how to lead on campus, career, and in the community

LINKEDIN LEARNING CHAMPIONS

LINKEDIN | 2020 - 2021

 Started a project to show the fun part of studying, throughout photoshoots showing scenes and picturesque approaches from the educational environment

TEAM LEADER AND USER INTERFACE DESIGNER

ADOBE CREATIVE JAM | 2019

 Gathered a team of four to create a full working prototype in less than 10 hours using the Adobe XD

CALLIGRAPHER

STARS IN JARS - ALGONQUIN COLLEGE | 2019

 Wrote 40 messages using different calligraphy styles to connect survivors of childhood cancer with children currently undergoing treatment in the Ottawa and Greater Toronto regions